Hurray! Hurray! Mashiron!
Hurray, hurray, Mashiron...
Hurray, hurray, Mashiron!
Keep it down.
What's this? Arisaka Mashiro got her
past and past perfect tenses mixed up!
Oh, right.
Arisaka usually doesn't wear
glasses, but she is for this fight.
I can't concentrate.
Also, my glasses are off-limits.
Why, oh why, has the tragedy by the
name of "makeup exams" befallen her?!
The high school curriculum is tough.
Oh, dear! Yet another mistake!
It's an elementary spelling error!
I asked you to teach me,
not do a running commentary!
Episode Four:
"Meat Makes Me Happy!"
I just barely passed.
It was touch and go for me too,
but I didn't fail any subjects.
You must be used to it by now, right, Bro?
Say, Masaya. Wanna know my scores?
No, I don't.
I bet most of them are perfect, anyway.
What's wrong?
P-Perfect?
Does such a score really exist in real life?
Don't overreact.
She'll let it get to her head.
You're so indiffurent.
So, you made it through
all right, didn't you?
Yeah, for what it's worth.
I hope Mashiro's hanging in there.
Having to take makeup exams is rough.
Tests are so cruel.
Her scores weren't all
that different from mine.
Makeups
English
Japanese History
I'm finally free.
Congrats!
Shall we go, then?
Okay, okay.
You'd better throw in some
feints, or I'll catch you!
Well, I'll run!
Hello!
Oh, hey, Arisaka.
Done with your makeups?
Yes. I can come back to
practice starting today, too.
What's going on here?
"What," you ask? Practice.
What's the goal of this regimen?
What effect will it have?
Is it a tactic devised to
take out a specific opponent?
First things first,
who are you?
Oh, my apologies.
Broadcasting
I'm Hosaka Minori, of Kunahama
High's Broadcasting Club!
Nice to meet you!
I've been wanting to cover the FC team,
which used to dead and buried, but has
recently poked its head out from the grave.
I figured I'd drop by and say "Hello" today.
I'm sorry. She's my classmate.
She asked me to give her access to the
team in exchange for helping me study.
Hell yeah! Our team's finally
getting press coverage, too!
Feel free to ask me anything
about speed and muscles!
The summer tournament's coming up next month.
Please tell us what you hope to achieve.
The Archipelago is a warzone
teeming with powerhouse schools.
On the other hand, our school's
team is a bunch of newbies.
Do you have some sort of secret plan?
Oh man, that stings.
What can ya do? It hurts because it's true.
Cutting to the chase, what
challenges are you facing?
Well, it's the rainy season,
so we're having a hard time because
we can't practice outside.
I see. That explains the indoor training.
Allow me to ask you once again:
What are they doing?
It just looks they're playing tag.
That's a mock battle of sorts in which
you're running instead of flying.
It helps hone dogfighting instincts.
Gotcha!
H-Huh?
What the...
What did you just do, Kurashina?
Good question.
She's got amazing jumping ability.
How could she do a backflip with
such ease from that situation?
She'd already improved a
lot at the training camp,
and she's gotten even better while
I was dealing with makeup exams!
Hey, that was incredible!
Did I surprise you, Tobisawa-san?
Who wouldn't be surprised by that?
I even surprised myself.
She did it unwittingly?
That's Kurashina-san for you.
All right! Take a breather!
Okay!
I'll go get changed!
So there's something I've
been thinking about.
Why don't we stop calling
one another by our surnames?
It's kinda awkward.
You've got a point there.
Acting too polite can delay a second's
instructions by a few seconds.
Not just that. I'd like the team
to bond more during practice.
I think that's a great idea!
In that case, please call me Asuka.
Then... Asuka?
Thank you, Misaki-chan!
Thanks...
Hold it right there!
I've been calling her Misaki-senpai for ages!
I'm the veteran here!
Oh, so that makes you my senpai.
That's right!
Let's get back to practice, then.
Okay.
All right! I'm gonna nail it this time!
I'll do my best, too!
Mashiro Udon
I died.
Mashiro, you're a fighter!
You can't beat her in a race!
Take a shortcut and ambush
her at the next line!
Got it!
Is she not good at initial movements?
Okay, that's enough!
Next up, Asuka and Misaki
in a practice match.
Mashiro, keep your basic posture in mind,
and do laps around the playing field.
I understand.
It's all about spirit, Arisaka!
Yeah, yeah.
On your marks...
Set!
That's the way, Asuka.
Okay!
What do you do when you're blocked off?
This!
You're really getting the hang of it.
You're mine!
If you'd quickly regained control there,
you could've still touched the buoy first.
Right!
When did Asuka-senpai get good enough
to keep up with Misaki-senpai?
I'm moving in for the touch.
Not so fast.
Misaki-chan really is awesome.
Hey, Masaya.
How many wins will I need
in order to face Shindou-san
in the summer tournament?
If you learn to use moves like that at will,
you'll run into him eventually.
Got it!
I'm gonna get left behind!
I learn a lot from watching
you fly, Misaki-chan.
You've gotten so much better, Asuka.
Until recently, you were having
trouble just flying straight.
Thanks, though I'm still
a bit unstable in flight.
Teach me how to do a barrel roll sometime!
It's like I'm
one of those players who get kicked from
party chat because their rank's too low.
Are you really okay with this?
You won't get to practice
with the others anymore.
Are you sure?
And not just practice. You won't
get to stay with them, either.
This way, Asuka!
Wait for me, Misaki-chan!
Thank you all so much!
Idol Misaki
Misaki Meet'n'Greet
Misaki Life
Idol Misaki
Meet'n'Greet
Not Accepting
Any More Fans
Fancy pasta's simply a must for lunch.
Udon's so old hat.
I would hate that to death!
Cleared fur takeoff!
Hey! Yer supposed to take
off from a terminal!
Jeez, she's so rowdy.
U-Um, I'm so sorry!
Hey—
Huh? You're Takafuji Academy's..
You're Kunahama's...
I-I have a favor to ask!
I challenge you to an unsanctioned match!
I need to clear quests in order to level up!
What?
I'm sorry for challenging
you out of the blue.
Don't be.
I've kinda run into a brick wall.
At FC?
Yes.
Misaki-senpai has always been good,
and even though Asuka-senpai
was a beginner like me,
she keeps improving at breakneck speed.
You see people like that every now and then,
but for most, daily practice is what counts.
I beg of you!
I wanna reach a level
where I won't be embarrassed
to practice with the team!
Please teach me some kind of ultimate move!
What are you talking about?
It's a no-go after all, huh?
You're a first-year like me, and yet
you're already a starter at Takafuji.
You're out of my league.
I'm not, really.
I just make sure I have
all the basics down pat.
All the basics down pat?
Yeah.
Could you help me with that?
Eh?
I wanna catch up to the others!
Please teach me the basics!
Our team's going to a training
camp starting next week,
but I can teach you until then.
Thank you so much!
I have to get my basics right.
What are membranes...
Style-specific adjustments...
Take the same flight path
and follow me, okay?
Wait, wait.
Isn't this practice for speeders?
I'm a fighter, though.
I'm not saying this because I'm a speeder,
but whatever your playing style,
you can't win if you lose
speed unnecessarily.
Got it.
Let's go again.
Basic rule: do not lose speed.
Relax your body.
'Kay!
Instead of ascending or descending sharply,
try to maintain smooth gradients.
Okay.
Mashiro Udon
Here ya go.
You could catch a cold like this,
so eat this and warm up.
Don't be shy now, Rika-chan.
Consider it thanks for teachin' her.
Meat makes me happy!
Time to dig in!
Let's eat!
How is it?
It's delicious!
Great.
You love meat, don't you?
I remember you eating lots during camp.
I'd love for you to come eat every day.
In return, help this girl
out with her studies.
You go to Takafuji, don't you?
Quit running your mouth, Mom!
Oh, and keep Rika-chan a
secret from the others.
Okay, okay.
Well, enjoy yerself.
I will. Thank you!
My mother's like that, too.
She gets really worried if I stay out late.
Wouldn't she be worried now, then?
I'll call her in a bit.
Want me to call yer mother, Rika-chan?
Enough already!
Closed for the day - Mashiro Udon
Stop meddling with people all the time!
You do it with Misaki-senpai, too!
What? Come on...
Is "Misaki-senpai" Tobisawa-san from camp?
Yeah. I picked up FC only
because she joined the team.
I envy you for having a role model.
You don't get along with Satouin-san?
She's really helpful, and I respect her.
But she's kinda out there, isn't she?
I guess.
Keep this between us,
but Satouin-senpai's
surname is actually just Satou.
So what, she just added the "in" herself?
Yep.
Maybe I should follow suit.
Arisakain!
Whoa, that sounds kinda awesome.
You should call yourself
Ichinosein, too, Rika-chan.
Eh? I-I think I'll pass.
Satouin-senpai has dibs on
"in," so she'll get mad at me.
You're so nice, Rika-chan.
Guess we'd better not, then.
You've been leaving in a hurry
after school these days.
Have I?
Is practice rough?
The summer tournament's almost here.
Did they tell you to show up early?
Nah, not at all.
Bye!
See you tomorrow!
Asuka!
Your center of gravity is all over the place.
R-Right!
Isn't that Mashiro-cchi?
Yeah.
When did her form get so pretty?
Mashiro Udon
That week just flew by, huh?
Thanks for teaching me,
even though you were busy.
Maybe I'll be on equal footing
with Asuka-senpai now.
I don't know about that.
I taught you only the basics.
Matches are a whole different beast.
Oh...
But I'm sure you'll be fine.
Hm?
Your light and petite
frame is your advantage.
It lets you change directions
without losing speed.
Okay, got it.
Well, see you—
Wait a minute!
I'm Jashin-chan, Mashiro's helpful sidekick.
But starting today,
I'm going to stay by your
side and help you, too.
Thanks!
But in return...
Mashiro says she wants to
form an alliance with you
and get much closer to you.
And asks if she can call you Rika.
Sure thing, Mashiro!
I hereby declare the Mashiro-Rika
First-Year Alliance formed!
Okay! To a long and fruitful alliance!
I had lots of fun.
I had fun, too.
Let's meet again at the tournament.
If you use the advantage
you have in your game,
you'll stand a chance against anybody!
Use the advantage I have in my game?
I don't get it.
That's it!
Two Weeks Until the Tournament!
Aim for the quarterfinals!
All right! As always, let's
practice with spirit!
Okay!
Do you have a moment, Masaya-senpai?
I need to talk to you about something.
Okay, on your marks...
Set!
Sh-She's so fast!
Mashiro...
Whoa!
I racked my brain to find my own style of play.
FC Walkthrough
My weaknesses:
Weak eyesight -> Slow reactions
Tiny frame -> Evasion +10
Wasn't Mashiro-chan a fighter?
She's pulling away!
Hurry up and take a shortcut!
R-Right!
Anyway, I have to head her off!
Mashiro-chan's so awesome.
Thanks for pointing out my advantage, Rika.
This suits me much better!
What's going on?
I don't believe it.
Mashiro came to me earlier, saying
she wanted to be a speeder.
She found her own flying style, huh?
Yeah.
Looks like she'll make a fine speeder.
I may be no good at all,
but I'm not going down without a fight!
She's not going to be able
to get past her this time.
I prepared an ultimate
move for times like these.
An ultimate move?
Look, flying fish.
What? Flying fish?!
Hook, line, and sinker!
That was...
The ultimate move of "Fireman,"
a legendary boxer and former super
welterweight world champion:
Distraction!
Oh, come on.
No way.
This match is over!
Arisaka Mashiro wins 4-0!
Where are you, flying fish?
Huh? Did you leave?
Flying fish!
Well, then. Here's to making the
summer tournament quarterfinals.
Let's eat!
The udon here really is delicious.
The stock in particular is out of the world.
Well, flyer stock is known to be tasty.
It's called that because it's so tasty,
it sends your worries flying, right?
That's one way to look at it.
What do you mean?
Flyer stock is stock made using flying fish.
Ah, I see.
Huh?
N-No way...
Want me to fly you home?
No, I'm fine.
See you tomorrow, then.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, flying fish.
But you were delicious.
She's got such pretty form.
Fl—
I've got mail.
It's from Mom.
My phone!
Here.
Th-Thank you.
The people here really are nice.
To Be Continued
Preview
Not knowing what the future holds is exciting.
Don't call me that!
Yes!
Yeah. Keep calm and carry on.
Episode Five:
"Yeah. Keep Calm
and Carry On."